Aidan Johnson

Spring 2024 Graduate

Skilled Programmer with over 4 years of C ++ programming experience. Logical and passionate professional with excellent problem-solving and time management skills. Team player dedicated to continuing education within the computer programming and gaming sector. Highly motivated programmer with experience in C++, Java, C#, and Python.

EXPERIENCE

Supplemental Instructor - *University of Houston, Victoria, TX*

02/2021 - PRESENT

- Coached learning developers on best practices in C++ programming, enhancing individual capabilities and productivity.
- Improved student retention through tailored one-on-one tutoring sessions for struggling individuals.
- Led several sessions with small groups to encourage communication and improve interpersonal relationships.
- Addressed common misconceptions and knowledge gaps during instruction sessions.

Games Attendant - Main Event Entertainment, San Antonio, TX

03/2017 - 01/2018

- Assisted in revenue generation through efficient handling of game transactions, including cash handling and prize distribution.
- Utilized effective communication skills when interacting with both guests and teammates, fostering positive relationships.
- Maintained a safe environment for guests by ensuring proper use of equipment and adherence to safety guidelines for Laser Tag and Gravity Ropes course.

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Science in Digital Gaming and Simulation

University of Houston, Victoria, TX

08/2019 - Current

- Accomplished student in Digital Gaming and Simulation, maintaining a 3.549 cumulative GPA
- Ran TTPRG campaigns in multiple RPG systems that apply practices learned in courses

High School Graduate - Roosevelt High School, San Antonio, TX

- Graduate of DATA Magnet Program
- Received multiple commendations and awards including 4 time recipient of PICK Award, Excellence in Video Game Design, and Excellence in Animation

San Antonio, TX 78258
Open to Relocation
(210) 862-8868
aidanjohnson151@gmail.com

SKILLS

Object-Oriented Programming

Strong Algorithm Knowledge

Programming Languages

Designing Core Gameplay Content

CODING LANGUAGES

Advanced:

C++

Intermediate:

C#

Java

Python

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Dean's List

Spring 2020

Fall 2021

Spring & Fall 2022

Spring 2023

President's List

Fall 2020

Fall 2023